[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Are you okay?
Yes, Mikoy. I'm just really, really happy.
Because my son is here with me,
along with my daughter.
It's a good thing the world is small.
Sen, look.
Oh.
If this works on Chiara, well and good.
If it doesn't, we still have Donabel.
Ouch, that hurts.
It's time, Chiara.
It's time for you to lead the Concordat.
Whatever you have here,
you need to leave it all behind,
as soon as possible.
In-law, is Chiara there?
Of course. It's her bridal shower tonight.
I just wanted to check on her.
She's excited about her wedding.
That's good to hear.
Okay, in-law. Thank you so much. Take care over there. Good night.
Wait, I have something--
Let's do a question-and-answer round so we can really get to know each other.
Okay!
Who can drink the most?
-Definitely you. -Wow, unbelievable.
She can really drink!
Here's the question.
Who kissed first?
Who was it?
-Oh. -Who?
-Who? -Who among you?
You!
It was me.
Bro, you're really handsome.
You're really something!
Right in Prague!
You're one of a kind, Mikoy!
Who fell in love first?
It was me. I'll admit it.
-That's me. -The lover boy!
-Yes, that's me. -Lover boy!
Seriously?
Who fell harder?
The truth.
I think I did.
Okay, this is it. This is the hardest one.
Who's the messier one?
This one is salty! This one!
Salty.
No!
Messy!
That's the salty one!
Salty?
Mikoy is the messy one.
I'm the messy one.
Yes, that's me.
Wait, why me?
It's my turn to ask…
That's really me!
Chiara and Mikoy.
Opposite!
-Chiara and Mikoy. -Chiara!
Who kissed first?
Whoa! You're the man!
He already asked that.
Did you already ask that?
Who closed their eyes first when they kissed?
You!
Why did you close your eyes?
That dried fish smells so good. I've missed this.
-Why? -Yes!
We're not allowed to cook this in our condo.
It's so good.
Angelito.
Make yourself some coffee first so you can get nervous about
what you did last night.
Wow, Angelito.
We never knew you were like that.
Like what?
Hey!
What?
Don't play innocent!
What are you guys talking about?
Huh!
Can we talk?
Then let's talk!
What do you want to talk about?
You know,
I'm pissed at you.
You think you're the only one?
Huh?
Me too.
But you know,
even though I'm pissed at you,
I still want to talk to you.
Huh?
Me too.
Even though every time I get close to you,
I get so damn annoyed.
Because…
you're an idiot!
Yes, I am.
I'm an idiot.
But… But…
I have a crush on you.
Really?
Yes.
You?
You're an idiot too!
Ow.
Because
I have a crush on you too.
So, we have a mutual crush, then?
-Like that? -Yes.
Mutual crush backing, padlock and key.
Look at you, coming up with stuff like that.
-Let's go back there. -Cheers.
Ow, ow, easy, easy.
Easy.
Is that how you eat in the condo?
Even with dried fish, you still use a spoon and fork?
We don't have a condo.
The eggs are so good.
Ow.
Dekyo's mix is seriously lethal.
It hurts!
Ow.
Oh my gosh.
Huh?
What's this?
What?
Congratulations for what?
You don't remember?
Angelito.
Just a moment, Father.
Don't leave yet.
Let me borrow this first.
Wow!
-All set, Father. -Okay.
Angelito.
Do you accept Sofie,
even though she eats all the food in the fridge?
There.
Good man!
And you, Sofie,
do you accept Angelito,
even though he sometimes smells like sunshine?
That's mine!
In that case,
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
Kiss her already!
Kiss her!
And for today's episode, of course, Mikoy and I are gonna play
1v1!
-Ball. -Your turn.
I'll film you guys. I'll film you guys.
You film us, Jen-Jen.
-Are you ready, Mikoy? -Let's go!
Defense!
Mikoy, you got this!
-Hey, my ball. -Brick!
-One point, one point. -What do you mean, one point?
That's my score. That's my score.
It was out!
I got one point!
A point for the brick.
Fine, fine. One point it is.
One point. I got one point.
Hey, Angelito!
-Come here. -Bro.
Angelito's here.
Come help us.
What's up? Where?
With what? Being handsome.
Doesn't seem necessary.
See?
Film it, film it.
How are we supposed to play basketball? We don't have a ball anymore.
It fell down over there, into the begtu.
Let's just make content.
-Content? What content? -Right.
Let's make content.
-Content? -Let's make content.
-You go here. Here. -Game.
-Let's keep going. -There.
It's simple. I'll teach you.
Okay.
‎Right. We can do that. Content.
‎Let's make content.
Why did you really come back, Mama Yaya?
You know why I came back.
After La Morte Bianca died,
someone took her place.
Rio De Janyx.
But he's not smart.
He's not careful.
But he's dangerous.
Many in the Concordat want you.
They want you to take his place.
But Rio De Janyx doesn't want any competition.
And you know what they do
to anyone they see as a threat.
-Look what we're doing! -I'm getting the hang of it.
No.
I'm never going back to that world, Mama Yaya.
Are you happy?
This is my life now.
But Chiara.
Mama Yaya.
This is what I chose.
You know,
I'm so grateful that you always come with me.
You know me, of course.
I'm getting older, but I'm still sexy.
So naturally, I have trouble carrying things.
You always carry them for me.
Why are you so quiet?
Is something wrong?
Nothing's wrong, Mommy Tess.
Um…
How was the party last night?
How come you didn't come?
I had some things to take care of, and Mom made us go somewhere.
You know, she's making the most of her vacation.
Of course. That's good. The timing is perfect.
And you know,
I'm really happy you got to spend time with your mom.
Yes, finally. Finally.
I honestly don't want her to leave again.
Of course.
But you know what I think?
You should invite her to the wedding.
What?
Of course.
And not just because she's your mother,
but because she's already part of our family.
After all, she is Chiara's Mama Yaya, right?
Really?
Of course. What are you talking about?
And you should tell her yourself, just to make sure she gets the invitation.
Oh, goodness.
Thank you, Mommy Tess. I'm sure Mom will be so happy.
And tell her she can't escape,
because I know she misses
all the Filipino food we serve at celebrations, right?
So she better eat as much as she can at the reception.
She definitely will. You know her, Mommy Tess.
She's actually the one who taught me
how to wipe out entire serving trays.
We've got plenty more trays to wipe out, so let's get going.
Well, let's see who you're hiding, Sean.
Babe, what are you doing here?
I thought you were leaving ahead of me.
You can't stay away from me.
You missed me already.
You can't leave me alone.
I knew it.
Oh.
Babe, what is this?
Babe, come on. Can we… Can we just talk like normal people?
Let me go, so we can talk normally, Carlota. Please.
Sean.
So,
either you come clean right now
and tell me
everything about the woman you've been talking to
or I'll make sure
you never get to cheat on anyone again.
There.
-There. -Okay.
There you go.
One, two, three. There!
This should be good for the goofballs, sweetheart.
Let's fix yours next.
The ones for your bridesmaids and maid of honor.
The world really is a small place, huh?
Who would've thought your Mama Yaya
would turn out to be Rahmboy's mother?
Even I was surprised.
By the way, sweetheart.
How come you never told me about your Mama Yaya?
Well, it just slipped my mind, sweetheart.
And besides, you know,
a lot of things happened between the two of us,
and to be honest, I just never thought we'd see each other again.
I'm glad you found each other again.
Right?
Ow.
Ouch!
-Sweetheart, I'm sorry. -Ow.
I thought there was, you know,
an insect.
-I thought there was a bug. -A bug?
I saw it. There it is.
I thought you were starting to miss your violent life.
That hurts!
I'd never miss that.
Really? My side seems to be telling me otherwise.
I'm just joking, sweetheart.
Of course, I know you're not going back to that life.
I know. This is where we belong.
Living the quiet life we've always dreamed of.
Right?
Don't stress about it, okay?
So playful.
So this is what having a family feels like.
If only I could,
I'd want things to stay this way.
Being with them.
And I will end anyone,
anyone who tries to disrupt our lives again.
Concordat.
Are you ready?
I hope so.
Let's hope Viktor and Donabel make it here.
Did you hear?
About ma'am's husband?
The one who used to be here.
Viktor Valtrovi.
Yes. It's pretty bad.
He's so beated.
What happened? Was there a riot?
All I heard was that he could barely stand.
We're screwed.
General Norberto might find out.
It's still unclear.
We still don't know if there was a rumble
or if he violated any rules in there.
Maybe we can talk to General Norberto?
There's an update.
Once our dreams finally come true.
I've found a new dream for myself.
I've built a new life that I want.
I held up my end, Chiara.
It's time for you to hold up yours.